[{"answer_text": "sherlock", 
"question_id": 31, 
"question_text": "Favorite Movie"}, 
{"answer_text": "seaweed snack", 
"question_id": 61,
"question_text": "Snack"}, 
{"answer_text": "arctic monkeys", 
"question_id": 111, 
"question_text": "Favorite Band"}, 
{"answer_text": "cubed set", "question_id": 101,
"question_text": "Hobby"}, 
{"answer_text": "mysql query optimization", 
"question_id": 51, "question_text": "Book"}, 
{"answer_text": "Zip ID Case", 
"question_id": 91, "question_text": "Daily Item"},
{"question_text": "Hobby", "answer_text": "magic tricks", "question_id": 1},
{"question_text": "Favorite Board Game", "answer_text": "cluedo", "question_id": 11},
{"question_text": "Favorite Band", "answer_text": "mumford and sons", "question_id": 21}, 
{"question_text": "Favorite Food", "answer_text": "cheescake", "question_id": 71}, 
{"question_text": "Wish Item", "answer_text": "tower drinking game", "question_id": 81}, 
{"question_text": "College Essentials", "answer_text": "vera bradley zip id case", "question_id": 111}, 
{"question_text": "Favorate Animal", "answer_text": "cow", "question_id": 91}, 
{"question_text": "TV Show", "answer_text": "friends", "question_id": 41}, 
{"question_text": "Gadgets", "answer_text": "sherlock bag", "question_id": 101}]